<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>unity on Sean D. Stach Blog &amp; Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://rhiyo.github.io/tags/unity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in unity on Sean D. Stach Blog &amp; Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 01:15:31 +1030</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rhiyo.github.io/tags/unity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>RuneCaster</title>
      <link>https://rhiyo.github.io/post/2020-12-11-runecaster/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 01:15:31 +1030</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhiyo.github.io/post/2020-12-11-runecaster/</guid>
      <description>Trailer LibGDX Demo Code  thisisthestartofsummary
RuneCaster started as a game project I developed at University based on an assignment I was given to build a mobile game using the Java library LibGDX. Mobile games weren&amp;rsquo;t something I personally played so it was a learning process for me and required me to look into and test other popular games on the platform. I wanted to make use a strength of mobile devices, the touch screen, so the main mechanic was to cast spells by drawing matching runes once prompted on the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heroes Trials</title>
      <link>https://rhiyo.github.io/post/2020-12-10-heroes-trials/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 02:02:32 +1030</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhiyo.github.io/post/2020-12-10-heroes-trials/</guid>
      <description>While living in Tokyo I volunteered for a convention “Tokyo Sandbox.” Which focuses on giving indie game developers the opportunity to show their work to game industry veterans and investors. During this event I met the developer for an RPG game called “Adel” at the time. They were looking for someone to develop the AI for their game which lead to me eventually working with him and his company Shinyuden. As of 2018 the game has been released on PlayStation, Switch, Steam and Xbox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3d Printing Simulation</title>
      <link>https://rhiyo.github.io/post/2020-12-10-3d-printing-simulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:28:01 +1030</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhiyo.github.io/post/2020-12-10-3d-printing-simulation/</guid>
      <description>Source Code Demo  thisisthestartofsummary
This project was developed for a university assignment to understand the use of game engines. The engine in this case being Unity. The task was to develop a 3D printing simulations using certain features of Unity. It had to be 3D with a first-person view point and keyboard-based locomotion. The 3D printer itself had to be controlled via an in-game button interface and the printing needed to be visualised in a unique way of my choice.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
